本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻译： 究焰 养兔子的格里森 栗子君 大豆唐 Ms无语 饭团 野兽派的小忧桑
校对： 小安   后期： 小蕾
噢 好极了 你又游手好闲
Oh, good, you're doing nothing.
我在看季后赛呢
I'm watching the playoffs.
上周日你也是这么说的
That's what you said last Sunday.
嘿...
Hey...
随便吧 反正我可是绞尽脑汁在想
Anyway, I've been kicking around some ideas
怎么通知亲朋好友我们的弄璋之喜
for birth announcements.
我只需要你再多签一个名
I just need you to sign off on one more thing.
你想要的都行 是在...
I'm sure whatever you want is fine, it's...
尼玛这是何物?
What the hell is that?
这是他受洗的时候拍照要穿的行头
It's his wardrobe for the christening announcement photo.
我勒个去
Oh, no.
我儿子可不穿那玩意儿
My son is not wearing that.
哦 别急别急 如果你担心这是个二手货的话
Oh, no, no, no... if you're afraid it's derivative,
这只是故意弄成这样的
it is intentionally so.
这可是以弗朗西斯・福特・科波拉
It is modeled after
导演的《德古拉伯爵》中
Lucy Harker's funeral gown
露西・哈克的寿衣为原型制作的
from Francis Ford Coppola's Dracula.
好好瞧瞧嘛 大卫
Good eye, David.
我儿子可不穿连衣裙 布莱恩
My son is not wearing a dress, Bryan.
这可不是连衣裙
It is not a dress.
这是具有划时代意义的经典晨衣
It is a classic turn of the century dressing gown.
是随处可见的婴儿装 而且很多夫妇
They were very common infant attire and a lot of parents
都让宝宝在弄璋弄瓦之喜和受洗礼上穿哦
still use them in birth and christening announcements.
我只是希望他第一个生日上
I'm just kind of hoping to get to his first birthday
不会有人叫他"小基"
without him being called "a baby homo."
谁会管一个婴儿叫"小基"
Who would call an infant "a baby homo"
难道是小版米歇尔・巴克曼不成?
except for a toddler Michele Bachmann?
大卫 人不靠衣装
David, clothes do not define what somebody is.
我是说 你瞧瞧我
I mean, look at me.
如果要你就我的穿着
If you had to pick what my sexuality was
判断我是直的还是弯的 你怎么看?
based on what I was wearing, what would you say?
娘炮版巴格・范斯
Lesbian bagger vance.
我喜欢你的打扮 我只是觉得
I love the way you dress, I'm just saying we have
我们要对自己给孩子的印象格外小心
to be careful about what kind of impression we put out there.
- 你想说啥? - 我想说人们第一反应
- Meaning what? - Meaning that people make snap judgments
总是以貌取人
based on appearances
这有可能会影响宝宝的一生
and it could affect him for the rest of his life.
好吧 如果你不喜欢我的想法
Fine, if you don't like my idea,
那你就自己想一个吧
come up with one of your own.
另类家庭 第一季第十四集
你好哇
Hello.
欢迎光临
Welcome.
简・福雷斯特 精致的房产
Jane Forrest, exquisite properties
总有一款适合您
for appropriate buyers.
额滴神呀 这里咋死气沉沉的
My God, it's dead in here.
像极了鬼屋
It's more like a haunted open house.
而你就是其中的一只鬼
And you must be one of the ghosts.
从你的装束看
Judging by your outfit,
不得不说就像阿尔戈号建成的那个年代
I'd say you died around the time argo was set.
我就这么穿了
I am dressed as what I am,
好的房产中介就该这么穿
which is a damn good real estate agent.
现在你是想在这看房
Now, are you here to view the property
还是想在这里大放厥词?
or just to air out those dazzling new tooth caps of yours?
噢 放轻松 小简 我是布赖斯
Oh, relax Janey, I'm Brice.
南希・奈尔斯的经纪人助理
Nancy Niles' broker associate.
她让我来看看你第一个开放参观日怎么样
She sent me here to check out your first open house.
让我们瞧瞧
Let's see.
看到没? 我刚刚...溜了一圈
You see that? I just... I just cruised myself.
简直就像个希腊之神
I am literally a Greek God.
你说我的
Tell me, does this
内裤是不是显得我很大呢?
pant make my package look too big?
显然和你的自负相比是相形见绌了
Certainly pales in comparison to the size of your ego.
好了 非常感谢你 普赖斯
Now, thank you very much, Price...
是布赖斯...和达拉斯・霍华德一个名字
Brice... as in Dallas Howard.
简 告诉我
So, Jane, tell me.
你想在哪开始你的房地产事业?
Where'd you get your start in real estate?
- 俄亥俄州 - 没错
- Ohio. - Right.
我敢说 这新鲜出炉的
And I bet the smell
曲奇香味就是
of these cookies baked fresh from a tube
你的秘密武器?
is your secret weapon?
- 没错 - 大错特错
- Yes. - No.
听着 这里是洛杉矶 这只会让你的客户
See, here in L.A. it's just a reminder of your client's
饮食失调 但是呢
eating disorder, but see
这不是让人们离开你的
that is not what's driving people
开放参观的原因
away from your open house.
好吧 别卖关子了 那是什么原因?
Okay, I'll bite... what is?
我们是可以随便涂层新的涂料
Well, we could quickly slap on a fresh coat of paint,
但我认为真正的原因在于基础
but I think the real problem lies within the foundation.
我是说 整个设计方案俗不可耐 陈旧过时
I mean, the whole design scheme is so tacky and outdated.
你脑残吗? 我们又不可能让栋房子活过来
Are you insane? We can't flip an entire house.
别走神 宝贝 我不是说房子
Keep up with me, honey... I'm not talking about the house.
我是说你
I'm flipping you.
真高兴和你见面 仙妮娅
It was so nice meeting you, Shania.
希望这个既定旅程玩得高兴
I hope you had fun on the set tour,
虽然我通常
though I don't normally
不怎么高兴
give it myself.
作为我老板代孕人的孩子
There are special privileges that come
当然会有些优待啦
with being the kid of my boss's surrogate.
你没其他孩子了是吧?
You don't have any more children, do you?
噢 没了
Oh, no.
好的 一会见啦
Okay, see you guys later.
嘿 姑娘们 抱歉打扰啦 照片十分钟后就好
Hey, girls, hate to interrupt but picture's up in ten
我们的明星需要补补妆
and our star needs to be touched up.
油脸可摸不上粉
Oily faces don't powder themselves.
是啊
No, they don't.
拜拜
Bye.
噢 我看起来怎么样?
Oh, how do I look?
很棒
Great.
我牙齿里没卡东西吧?
Is there something in my teeth?
- 有口气吗? - 你刚吃腊肠了么?
- How's my breath? - Did you eat bologna?
那是克里斯
That's Chris.
他是一名场务
He's a grip.
- 什么是场务? - 你问倒我了
- What's a grip? - Got me.
我们还有点事要说
We have a bit of a thing going.
噢 嗯 达尼尔怎么样了?
Oh, um, what about Darnell?
我以为你们还热乎着呢
I thought you guys were hot and heavy.
我们关系更进一步后 达尼尔总是像辆
Well, when things got intimate, Darnell kept taking
开往市中心的公交车 没错我是喜欢
the bus downtown, which I do like,
但是他总是该停站的时候不停
but he never got off at the right stop.
结果一路开到了贫民区
He kept taking it all the way to skid row.
我都没法和他对视了
I couldn't look him in the eye anymore,
- 明白我在说什么吧? - 完全不明白
- you know what I'm saying? - Not at all.
- 嘿 小女孩 - 嘿
- Hey, baby girl. - Hey.
嘿 亲亲 MUA MUA
Hey. Kisses... mm-wah, mm-wah.
两件事... 第一 你看起来惊艳至极
Two things... number one, you look stupid fierce.
第二 我们有约了... 玛莉・布莱姬
Number two, we have a date... Mary J. Blige
在那玩手机呢 不准说不 还有
is playing at the Nokia, no is not an option, and...
不准谈电视剧
No more drama.
不介绍介绍这两位可爱的小姐吗?
Aren't you gonna introduce me to these two lovely ladies?
噢 克里斯 他们是我的朋友
Oh, Chris, these are my friends.
格尔蒂和仙妮娅
This is Goldie and Shania.
我猜你一定让男孩子们伤心欲绝吧
I bet you break boys' hearts left and right.
你难道不懂么 姐们儿?
Don't you know it, girlfriend?
我们找天出去钓凯子吧
We should go out boy-hunting sometime.
有点早熟是吧?
Isn't she precocious?
这词她四岁的时候教我的
She taught me that word when she was four.
好吧 我要回去工作了
Yeah, well, I better get back to work.
我要去控制摇臂
I got a jib arm to rig.
你什么意思 说要和我的男朋友
What was that, saying you want to go hunting
出去钓凯子?
for boys with my boyfriend?
罗基 我只是开玩笑罢了
Rocky, I was kidding.
我还太小 进不了同志吧
I'm too young to get into gay bars.
好了 照片好了
All right, picture's up.
好的 我们要让她的样子更现代
Okay, we want to upgrade her look.
但别弄那些非主流
But I don't want anything crazy.
你已经很非主流了 女士
Crazy is what you've got, girl.
我明白 但是这造型略显单薄
I know, it's so brittle, I just want
我想试试更短的造型 蒸片刻后
To snap it off, boil it in water
接着加点别的花样儿
And put marinara on it.
- 宝贝 瞧你这嘴皮子功夫 - 你懂个屁
- Baby, the way your tongue works. - You don't know the half
你可以弄点纹理和小卷
Maybe you just try adding a little texture and swing.
我妻子弄得就很性感
It looks hot on my wife.
这样头发披下来适合工作
It's easy to wear it down for work.
扎起来可以在家追孩子
Or tie it up for chasing our kids around the house.
我们就稍微弄点层次感
I say we do some subtle layering.
凸显你的下颌线
Something to highlight your great jaw line.
娜塔莎 原来你头发那么软啊
Natasha, I never noticed how soft you hair is.
不告诉我你护发素的牌子我就不走
Don't let me leave without the name of your conditioner.
还有你的手机号
And your phone number.
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
当然是希望能拿到她的电话啊
Hopefully getting her number.
你把这当作游戏?
And it's a game?
亲爱的 这当然是个游戏啊
Oh, sweetheart, it's definitely a game.
是嘛 那你期望的结局是?
Uh-huh, to what end?
结局嘛... 我咋知道
To what... I don't know.
可能是共进晚餐 看场电影 或者一切随天意
Go to dinner, a movie, or see where the night takes us.
爷可是有艘船呢
I have a boat.
你有没有站在她的角度想过?
Are you even thinking about her?
你有没有考虑过她的想法?
What about her feelings?
如果她是真的喜欢你呢?
What if she likes you?
你是不是被这里的烟熏晕了?
Is it the fumes in here?
我知道雷伯恩用的是两步法的乳化染色剂
I know rayburn uses a two-step emulsifying bleach.
得了吧 你这种人我见多了 布赖斯
Please, I know you, Brice.
你和我老公就是一个类型的人
I was married to a man just like you.
我觉得你既残忍又自私
And I think you are cruel and you are selfish.
如果你是正人君子的话
And if you were a decent human being,
就不会去骚扰那个女孩
you would leave that young girl alone
而是集中精力找你的同道中人
and stick to your own kind.
我的同道中人?
What's my own kind?
- 基佬 - 我才不是基佬呢
- Gay. - I'm not gay.
少装了 你手上戴着的链子可出卖了你
Oh, please, you are wearing a bracelet.
简 时代不同了
Jane, it's a new world.
你不能再因为一个男人对时尚和文化感兴趣
Just because a guy's into fashion and culture
或是他的发型 就断言他是基佬了
and hair processing doesn't make him gay.
我可听到了哟
Hear, hear.
你说大卫是抽的哪门子风?
I mean, what is David's problem?
这件可爱的晚礼服无论穿在
That's a perfectly lovely gown
男孩或者女孩身上都很好看
for a boy or a girl.
额 在这件事上我也许比较同意大卫的看法
Um, I think I might have to side with David on this one.
这衣服是有点... 女性化?
It's a little... girly?
那又怎样? 一个人的穿着没必要
Well, so what? I mean, clothing doesn't necessarily
体现出性别之分吧
have to indicate gender.
话是这样说 但是...
Right, but, um...
并不是每个人都能像你这样前卫
Most people aren't that evolved.
他们一般靠的就是第一印象
They go with their first impressions
第一印象不好 就会造成孩子心灵的创伤
and sometimes that can hurt.
我要和你家孩子聊聊
I need to talk to the child.
小屁孩 你竟然觉得
Child, you have lost your damn
我男朋友克里斯是基佬 你脑子是被门夹了吧
stinking mind suggesting that my boyfriend Chris is a homosexual.
这么说他不仅没出柜
Oh, so he's secretly gay,
而且还和女人约会来掩盖真相喽?
but dates women as a cover?
毕竟还是低调点好嘛
You know, on the down low?
什么? 低调?
What? The down low?
我男人可高调了... 他肯定是直男
My man is on the up high... he is straight.
我就知道你以为他是直男 罗基
I'm sure you think he is, Rocky,
但是我的基佬雷达可是很准的哦
but my gaydar is pretty impeccable.
怎么了 仙妮娅小姐?
Yes, miss Shania?
迭戈 我有话想对你说
Diego, I wanted to tell you.
尽管你们这类人想要在社会上向大家
Despite how difficult it must be in your community
公开自己的身份绝非易事
to proudly declare who you are,
但我已经知道了
I know.
你是指同志?
Homo?
我知道把手巾放在左口袋里
I know the hanky in your left pocket
就暗示着你是同志
is part of the gay hanky code.
这 我只是想在修剪杂草时 用它来擦擦汗
Well, I just, uh, use it to wipe my sweat when I trim the bushes.
好吧 我相信你
Okay, we'll go with that.
我把这个送给你吧
Here, I got you this.
这是布莱恩买的转录版的悲惨世界
It's Bryan's screener for Les Miz.
可能你认识的人里有喜欢看这个的吧
Maybe you know someone who'd enjoy watching it.
我能察觉到任何的蛛丝马迹
I just know on, like, a molecular level.
抱歉 罗基 但克里斯真的是基佬
Sorry, Rocky, but Chris is gay.
简 你干嘛要带个头巾? 装暴发户?
Ooh, Jane, what's with the scarf? Chemo?
我可没谢顶哦
My hair is not thinning,
如果你是在暗示这个的话
if that's what you're implying.
罗基怎么满头大汗的?
Why is Rocky sweating?
哦 仙妮娅觉得罗基的男朋友
Oh, well, Shania accused Rocky's boyfriend
是个基佬... 事实并不是这样
of being gay... Which he is not.
所以我们在这里 把事情都说清楚
And we were just, uh, clearing up the situation.
我现在也正处于同样的境地
I am going through this exact same thing
他是我的一个同事
with this fellow at work.
现如今 要断定一个人是基佬
Well, it's not as easy to tell who's gay
还是直男已经没那么容易了
and who's straight anymore.
如果连我都有点晕
If I'm confused,
就更不敢想象你们直人的感受了
I can't imagine how you straights feel.
反正克里斯是直男
Well, Chris is straight.
但是你的那个直男
Well, your not-gay,
基佬男友绝对不可能
gay boyfriend can't be
比布赖斯更基情
any gayer than gay Brice.
你怎么突然关心起这个了?
Why do you even care?
我得确定我到底是该喜欢他还是讨厌他
I need to find out if I should like him or hate him.
然后矫正一下他的三观
And make him deal with his life choices
以免伤及无辜的女人
so he doesn't hurt innocent women.
比如我
Like me.
对了 要不我们一起吃顿饭
Ooh, what if we have a dinner,
这样我们就可以对这些男的
and then we can put these guys
进行基佬测试... 就像游戏竞赛节目那样
to a gay test... like a game show.
- 呜呼! - 我同意
- Whoo-hoo! - Well, I'm in.
因为我确信我赢定了
Because I know I'm gonna win.
我也加入 为了弄清真相 让我做什么都行
Okay, I'll do anything to find out the truth.
如果这个点子奏效的话 我就把它
If this works, I can repackage it
和那些老古董一起打包卖给福克斯电视台
with has-beens and then sell it to FOX.
海滩别墅 我来啦!
Beach house!
我找到了最适合
I found the perfect
我们孩子在拍出生照时穿的衣服了!
outfit for the birth announcement picture.
不错吧? 我本来还打算
Huh? I was gonna get
买个小型护口器呢 但后来我发现
a little mouth guard, but then I realized
他还没长牙齿 所以用不着护口器 那么
he's not gonna have any teeth to protect, so...
这好歹比那个裙子好看啊
Well, it beats the dress.
那不叫裙子 叫晚礼服
It's not a dress, it's a gown.
这两者是不一样的
And there's a difference.
可不嘛 一个是女孩穿的 一个是基佬穿的
Yeah, one is for girls, the other's for gays.
天啊
Wow.
我只是想过我想要的生活
I'm just trying to live my life.
我才发现原来和我
I didn't realize I was
住在一起的人竟然恐同啊
living it with a homophobe.
小布 我不是那个意思
That's not what I meant, Bry.
我只是觉得 让人们来参加一个
I'm just saying, it's gonna be weird enough
有两个爸爸的孩子的弄璋之喜
for some people to receive a birth announcement
就已经够奇怪的了
with two dads on it.
天啊 大卫
Oh, my God, David.
如果你真的担心
If you're so concerned
其他人有什么想法的话
about what other people might think,
那我就在礼服背后写上
I'll just write on the back of it,
"这是件晚礼服 并且他不是基佬"
"it's just a gown. He's not gay."
至少那时还不是
At least, not yet.
"不过到了青春期就不好说了"
"We'll check back at puberty."
你能不拿这个开玩笑吗?
Please, don't even joke about that.
那些对我们评头论足的人
All the people who judge us
到时肯定会站出来说 "瞧见没有?"
will get on their soapboxes and say, "see?"
"因为孩子周围有太多的基情因素
"He was surrounded by so much gay,
所以孩子本身也受到了影响"
it probably rubbed off on him."
那我父母的直人因素围绕我
Just like my parents surrounded me
这么多年了 怎么我还是成了基佬?
with all their straightness, and it rubbed off on me?
事物根本就不是那样发展的 大卫
It doesn't work that way, David.
我知道 但你也知道这是个现实的世界
Yeah, but you know how the world is.
人们就是喜欢谴责
People like to condemn
那些他们无法理解的事物
the things they don't understand.
之前有个...
There was this...
...男孩 他是我们初中模联的队员
...kid on my junior high mock U.N. team.
我叫他死基佬
I called him a fag,
因为我很害怕
'cause I was afraid
人们有一天也会那样叫我
that people would call me that.
虽然那时还小
'Cause even back then,
但我很清楚我就是同志
I knew that I was one.
我希望...
I hope...
我们的儿子不要再经历
Our son won't experience the same
我们经历过的痛苦 羞辱和孤立
pain and humiliation and exclusion that we did.
大卫
David,
我并不担心这些
I'm not concerned about that,
因为我坚信
because I do believe
父母是会影响孩子的
that a kid's parents rub off on them.
但是我们教会他们的应该是
But the things that are gonna rub off on our kids
像坚强
are things like strength
容忍和爱心这样的品质
and tolerance and love.
我们晚点再讨论这个事吧?
Can we talk more about this later?
好的
Sure.
大家晚上好 欢迎来到...
Good evening, and welcome to...
"是基是直?!"节目现场
"Gay or not gay?!"
呃 你们确定要搞这个?
Yeah, are you guys sure this is a good idea?
- 确定 一定 - 以及肯定
- Yes. Yes. - Yeah.
简
Jane.
哦 天啊
Oh, my lord,
你看起来
you look
美极了
amazing.
我很少用很"赞"
I do not use the word "fabulous"
这个形容词...
very often...
好吧 也不是很少啦
Okay, maybe I do.
但这一次用它绝对是史上最合适的
But I've never meant it more than I do right now.
真的? 穿着这个
Really? I feel
我觉得好没女人味
so unladylike in these clothes.
回去换也来不及了 是吧?
It's too late to go home and change, right?
男士们快到了吧 好吧
Boys are coming soon. Okay.
这个基佬测试是怎么做的?
How does the gay test work?
我们设计了一系列的测试
Okay, we've devised a series of tests
来判断你们的男人是直是弯
to see which way your men sway.
我们准备最先抛出的话题是...
The first topic we're gonna throw at them is...
女性奥斯卡奖获得者
Female Oscar winners.
真相就要大白了
Dead giveaway.
您请
Here you go.
您真绅士啊
That's very gentlemanly of you.
如果你知道我在惦记着你这身打扮
If you knew what I was thinking about your new look,
你就不会说我绅士了
you wouldn't call me a gentleman.
你这样实在太性感了 简
You look hot as hell, Jane.
对我来说这就有点异性恋的意味了
Now that seemed like genuine boy-girl stuff to me.
你的观察雷达怎么样了?
What's your man-tenna picking up?
再给我点时间
I need more time.
好啦 各位 布莱恩拿手的松露龙虾酱
Okay, guys, we have Bryan's famous gruyre crisps
格鲁耶尔干酪薯片来啦
with a truffled-lobster paste.
- 噢! - 我厨艺不错哦
- Ooh! - I'm a great cook.
明天再开始节食吧
Diet starts tomorrow.
哔 哔 哔 哔
Beep-beep-beep-beep.
你不是过敏吗?
Aren't you allergic?
说到过敏
Speaking of allergies,
我一看到迪亚波罗・科蒂在2008年
I about busted out in hives when I saw
奥斯卡奖上穿的衣服 都要出麻疹了
what diablo Cody was wearing to the 2008 oscars.
有人记得吗?
Anybody remember?
噢 我的天
Oh, my God,
那条及地豹纹长裙?
that floor-length cheetah-print frock?
她看着像个带纹身的廉价沙发
She looked like a thrift store sofa with tattoos.
嗯 欢迎来到丛林 亲爱的
Hmm. Welcome to the jungle, honey.
我有点搞不懂 不过他上钩了
Very confusing. He took the bait,
但他把话题抛给了枪与玫瑰
but then he threw in that reference to guns n' roses.
抛给了什么?
To what?
算了
Never mind.
吃沙拉的时候 我们进行第二轮测试
Over salad, we'll initiate round two of testing,
依据同性恋男人的天赋
based on gay men's innate ability
猜猜排名前十的歌曲
to identify any top ten song.
格尔蒂 我们需要你帮个忙
Goldie, we'll need your help with this.
这个绿色女神色拉酱好好吃
This green goddess dressing is delicious,
- 本人很满意 - 噢 谢谢
- and Chris is delighted. - Oh.
哦 呃 吃沙拉的时候
Oh, uh, I always enjoy music
我喜欢听音乐
with my salad.
布莱恩 能不能把收音机打开?
Bryan, would you turn on the radio?
等等 妈 我带了竖笛哦
Wait, mom, I brought my recorder.
你们愿意听我吹嘛?
Would you like to hear me play it?
好啊! 等等 我想到了 咱们来玩个游戏吧
Great idea! Wait. I know. Let's make a game out of it.
辨声识曲!
Name that tune!
耶! 好 开始吧
Yay! Oh, play it.
蕾哈娜的
"Diamonds."
"钻石"
By Rihanna.
拜托 才两个音符 什么歌都有可能啊
Come on. It was two notes. It could be any song.
有可能 但这首不可能
It could, but it isn't.
他说对了
He's right.
蕾哈娜实在是太性感了
That Rihanna. Is so hot.
接下来是甜点时间
And then, for dessert,
我们到客厅去玩一个令人振奋的游戏 名人汇
we'll retire to the parlor for a rousing game of celebrity!
名人汇? 什么来的?
Celebrity? What's that?
名人汇是猜人名 就是从橘色鲍尔曲奇罐里
Celebrity is a guessing game, where you draw names out
抽一个名字 然后尽力
of an orange Bauer cookie jar, and then you try
让你的队友猜出你手里的名字
to get your teammates to guess the names that you're holding.
布莱恩和我会预先布局
Bryan and I will stack the deck
用一些关于同性恋的人物
with some very gay-centric personalities.
好啦 布赖斯 克里斯
All right, Brice, Chris,
组队完毕 来吧
our team is up, let's do it.
你们输定了 瞧瞧专业的
You guys are going down. Watch a professional.
开始啦
Here we go.
仙妮娅 准备好了我们就开始
Shania, whenever you are ready.
好的 来吧
All right, here we go.
好 他是个演员
All right, this guy is an artist
或者说是个摄影师...
or a photographer...
- 罗伯特・梅普尔索普! - 完全正确
- Robert mapplethorpe! - Yes.
好的 下一个是?
Okay, what do we got?
我不知道这是谁
I don't know who this person is.
名字开头是...接近"袋鼠"...
First name starts with, is like "kanga..."
- 露! - 麦克拉纳罕!
- Rue! - McClanahan!
对啦! 没错!
Yes! Bam!
好啦 这个是某人的女儿
Okay, all right, this is the daughter of someone.
- 莱莎・明奈利 - 麦当娜
- Liza Minnelli. - Lourdes Ciccone.
是麦当娜
It was lourdes.
太厉害了
That's amazing.
嗯 这个简单 是我写的
Okay, oh, this one's easy, this one's mine.
他是德州农工队四分卫 海斯曼奖杯的得主
This was the quarterback for the aggies, heisman trophy winner.
约翰尼・曼齐尔
Johnny Manziel.
时间到
Time.
那如果这些都测完了
Okay, so after all that,
结果还不能确定呢?
what if the data is inconclusive?
还有一个终极测试
There is one, final test.
测试结果百分百准确
It is absolutely 100% accurate.
但如果他不是同性恋的话
But it is so horrible
让他经受这些也是很痛苦的
to make a man sit through if he's not gay.
我只会把它当成终极武器
I will only break this out as an absolute last resort.
奥普拉的传奇舞会
Oprah's legends ball.
任何直男都不可能看完整部
No straight male has ever sat through an entire viewing
而没有任何崩溃迹象
without his body shutting down to protect itself.
还有 没错 西瑟莉・泰森也会出现
And, oh, yes, there will be Cicely Tyson.
啊 上帝啊 快看他们穿着最好的衣服
Ay, dios mio.Look at them sitting there
坐在奥普拉门前草坪上的样子!
in their Sunday best on Oprah's front lawn!
噢! 李奥汀・普莱丝小姐 来啊 妹子
Ooh! Miss Leontyne Price. Work it, girl.
菲利西亚・拉斯海德 你要是我妈就好了
Phylicia Rashad, I wish you were my mom!
滚出荧幕吧 玛丽亚・施赖!
Get off the screen, Maria Shriver!
噢 这是我最爱的场景
Ooh, this is my favorite part.
他们把话筒递给了帕蒂・拉贝尔小姐
They pass the microphone to miss Patti LaBelle!
- 唱吧 妹子! - 唱吧!
- Sing it, girl! - Sing it!
- 完啦! - 啊!
- It is over! - Ah!
我要去弄点白兰地喝
I'm gonna get a teensy Brandy.
噢 莲纳・荷恩 你太棒了!
Oh, Lena horne, you're alive!
貌似你的同伴已经
It looks like your fella's
挥起彩虹投降旗了
waving the rainbow flag in surrender.
还不能下定论呢 简
We don't know that for sure, Jane.
- 戴拉・里斯小姐 - 嗯!
- Miss della Reese. - Mm!
为什么不直接问他呢 罗基?
Why don't you just ask him, Rocky?
是啊 那不是比玩这些傻东西强多了?
Yeah, isn't it more honest than playing this silly game?
不行 我问不出口
I can't. It's too hard.
- 噢 唱啊 黛安娜 唱吧 - 你太棒了
- Oh, sing it, Diana, sing it. - You look crazy.
不 这个基佬测试挺有效啊
No, the gay test is working.
我们玩到结束吧
Let it play out.
原来是这样啊 基佬探测行动?
So that's what this is, a bitch-hunt?
呃 我知道我算什么了 我走了
Well, I already know what I am, so I'm gonna go.
挺好 格拉迪斯
Looking good, Gladys,
不错 很好 她又上去了
looking good. Nice. She's back on top.
布赖斯?
Brice?
拜托 别走啊
Please don't go.
简 我以为你很聪慧 有趣 精明
You know, Jane, I thought you were sharp and funny, shrewd,
而且你的新造型非常性感
with this new look of yours, super sexy,
但你居然办这个派对
but this little dinner party you're throwing
企图看看我是不是基佬?
to find out if I'm gay?
实在是可悲
That's pathetic.
哦 受不了了! 克里斯 你到底是直是弯?
Aw, hell! Chris, are you gay or straight?
我是什么?
Am I what?
你是基佬还是直男?
Are you gay or straight?
因为我们的游戏没什么用
Because this game we're playing
如果我们要在一起的话
isn't working and if we're gonna be a thing,
我必须弄清楚 现在!
then I need to know. Now!
好吧 我才不屑回答你的问题 罗基
Well, I don't think I care to answer that question, Rocky
但我要告诉你 你和我
I will tell you this though: You and I
绝对不是那么回事
are most definitely not a thing.
再没不是了
Not anymore.
格尔蒂 我很抱歉昨晚把仙妮娅
Goldie, I'm so sorry I involved Shania
牵扯进那个基佬雷达晚餐
in that gaydar dinner last night.
我们不仅伤害了别人的感情
We hurt people's feelings
还给人留下了丑恶的印象
and we perpetuated ugly stereotypes.
作为道歉 请接受
As an apology, please accept
这些法国拉杜丽薰衣草蛋白杏仁饼干
these French lavender macaroons from Laduree.
不 不 不 太漂亮了 吃了可惜
Neh, neh, neh, they're too beautiful to eat.
我好愧疚
I'm so ashamed.
我搞砸了罗基和克里斯的关系
I messed up Rocky's relationship with Chris,
而且我可能真看错他了
and I might have been wrong about him.
可能我不是真的拥有什么神奇的基佬雷达
Maybe I never really had an amazing gaydar power at all.
我要在博客上写封道歉信
I'm going to write a letter of apology on my blog
给波特兰市
to the city of Portland
因为我说那里所有女的都是同性恋
for describing its entire female population as lesbian.
真感人 宝贝
That's very sweet, baby.
现在的人都是性向成迷
It's a whole new sexually ambiguous world
那样很好
out there, and that's good.
我是说 没人能百分百确定我是基佬
I mean, no one can be 100% sure that I'm gay.
- 当然 - 是啊
- Sure. - Yes.
但是我...
But I...
- 我能不能...? - 别想...
- Can I...? - Don't even...
抱歉
I'm sorry.
好了 上午的工作就到这里 各位
All right, that's a wrap, folks.
一小时午餐时间
Take an hour for lunch.
克里斯 我做错了
Chris, what I did was wrong.
我不应该隐瞒你真正的晚餐意图
I shouldn't have lied to you about the auspices of our dinner.
我真的很抱歉
I am truly sorry.
我没资格指责你撒谎
I've got no right to criticize you for lying.
罗基 我是同性恋
Rocky, I am gay.
我没有经常公开提及
I don't say that aloud too often,
因为你看看和我一起工作的人
'cause look at this crew I work with.
这儿简直就像公鸭王朝
It's like duck dynasty up in here.
而且我们相处很愉快 所以我没告诉你
And I didn't tell you 'cause we were too busy having fun.
但是当我发觉你对我有那种意思时
But when I realized that you had those kind of feelings for me,
我不知道怎么告诉你真相又不会伤害你
I didn't know how to tell the truth without hurting you.
好吧 现在我知道真相了 我仍然需要你
Well, now that I know the truth, I still want you in my life,
只是不作为男朋友
but just not as a boyfriend.
我还能叫你"女朋友"吗?
Can I still call you "girlfriend"?
噢 我强调一下 告诉你一件事
Oh, I insist. And let me tell you something:
我是"歌唱吧!"的制作人 那意味着
I am a producer of Sing! And that means
我在这儿有说话权
I contribute to the order up in here.
如果有任何人因为你的性向
And if any person makes you feel uncomfortable
让你不痛快
because of who you are,
你马上来告诉我 我会秉公处理
you run and tattle to me and I will bring the justice.
好的
Okay.
在明天玛莉・布莱姬的演唱会之前...
And also before the Mary J. Blige concert tomorrow...
嘻哈女神?
Manis and pedis?
姐妹儿 冷静点
Girl, calm down.
我们要共进晚餐
We're doing dinner.
我很荣幸
I'd love that.
很好 明天见
Good. See you tomorrow.
美女 你的美臀还是那么性感
Girl, that ass is still banging.
我听说你你在格兰特上卖出了那套房子
I heard you sold that house on Glendower.
恭喜你
Congratulations.
谢谢
Thank you.
还有什么事吗?
Anything else?
没了
No.
- 其实 有 - 噢 是吗?
- Actually, yes. - Oh, yeah?
需要我告诉你米科诺斯岛上最好的酒吧吗?
Would you like some tips on the best bar in Mykonos?
或者我们可以玩女神嘎嘎冷知识
Or maybe we could play some Lady Gaga trivia.
或者也许你想知道
Or perhaps you're looking for some tips on how to remove
怎么洗掉窄脚牛仔裤上的酒渍?
Merlot stains out of skinny jeans?
我想和你谈谈昨晚的事情
I wanted to say something to you about last night.
我想和你道歉
I wanted to say I was sorry
我做的事很不光彩
and that what I did was not kind.
那你为什么还要做?
Then why did you do it?
我想要知道你是基佬还是直男
I needed to know if you were gay or straight.
噢 老天 你那么快就开始评判每个人
Oh, my God, you are so quick to judge everyone.
你想要给每个人贴上某些老套的标签
You want to label everyone up against some old stereotype.
你是我这辈子见过最刻板的人
You are the most stereotypical person I've ever met in my life.
你为什么在意别人是什么样?
What do you care what anyone is?
为什么在意我是什么样?
Why do you care what I am?
因为我喜欢你 因为我...
Because I like you. Because I'm d...
我迷上你了
I'm drawn to you.
我很爱我丈夫埃德加
I really loved my husband, Edgar.
真的
I really did.
我们在一起度过了最美好的时光
We had the best time together.
我们会一起去电影院
We would go to the theater,
一起发现新的小酒馆
we would discover new bistros.
我深陷其中
I was so attracted to all that.
但埃德加却没有...为我痴迷
But Edgar was not attracted... To me.
我不想再犯一次同样的错误
And I do not want to make that same mistake twice.
简 世界变了
Jane, the world has changed.
世界不是非黑即白
It's not black and white anymore.
对我来说 世界变得太多了
Well, maybe it's just too much change for me.
坐下吧
Sit down.
我可以帮你改变发型
I can help you change your hair,
我可以帮你改变穿着
I can help you change your outfit,
但只有你能改变你自己
but only you can change yourself.
你得问问你自己
The question you have to ask is
你是想继续坚持过去的一切是是非非呢
do you want to hold onto the way things used to be and be right,
还是想改变 变得幸福?
or do you want to change and be happy?
还觉得我是基佬么?
You still think I'm gay?
老娘不在乎了
I don't care.
那么 我一直在想我们孩子
So, I have been thinking about the outfit
在弄璋之喜上穿的衣服
our baby will wear for the birth announcement.
噢 亲爱的 我真不觉得这事有多重要
Oh, sweetie, I really don't want this to be a whole thing.
所以你想让他穿什么就穿什么
So he can wear whatever you want him to wear.
你怎么改主意了?
What made you change your mind?
那个愚蠢的晚餐聚会
That silly dinner party.
昨晚 我又变成了那个初中小屁孩
Last night, I became that kid from junior high all over again.
评判着别人 因为怕自己被评判
Judging someone because I was afraid of being judged.
不只是你
It wasn't just you.
还有仙妮娅
It was Shania, too.
如果我们不改变 不进化 我们就会死
If we don't change, if we don't evolve, then we die.
你现在没看见兽脚类恐龙在外边乱晃了
You don't see any theropod dinosaurs hanging around
不是吗? 你知道为什么吗?
anymore, do you? You want to know why?
因为驰龙科...
Because dromaeosauridae...
噢 老天 大卫
Oh, my God, David, it's like you want me
你想分散我的注意力吗
to stop paying attention.
我不想要我们的儿子
I just don't want our son
有和我一样的成长经历
to grow up the way that I did:
害怕做自己
Afraid to be myself,
循规蹈矩 以防被人评判
playing into stereotypes so he won't be judged.
但只要我不害怕 他就可以那样做
But he can only do that if I'm not afraid.
所以 来吧
So, go ahead.
让我们的儿子穿上裙... 礼服
Put our son in the dress... gown.
但我做了个小小的改动
But I do have one slight adjustment.
太完美了
It's perfect.
既古怪又惊艳 会让大家凌乱的
It's odd and amazing, and it will confuse everyone.
不过我喜欢
And I love it.